highlightsfootball.com 2019-04-26

# Privacy Policy - Highlights Football

## **Your choices**

You have the following rights concerning our processing of your personal data:

  1. the right to request access to your personal data as well as its rectification, removal or restriction of processing,
  2. the right to object to the processing,
  3. the right to transfer data,
  4. the right to withdraw consent for the processing of personal data for a specific purpose, if such consent has been previously given,
  5. the right to bring a complaint to the supervisory authority in connection with the processing of personal data.

The above mentioned rights can be exercised in accordance with the rules described in art. 16 – 21 of GDPR, by contacting us through contact form found on our website [http://highlightsfootball.com](https://highlightsfootball.com/contact-us/). We may refuse to exercise certain rights from those indicated above in a situation where the implementation of a given right would be in conflict with the legitimate purpose of the data we process. For example, we may refuse to delete personal data specified in your order until the expiry of the limitation period for claims under the concluded contract. We may contact you to ask you for further information to help you exercise your legal rights, or to speed up our response. We will try to respond to requests within one month and we will let you know if we need to take longer, for example because your request is complicated.

**Opt out of communications.**  You may opt out of receiving promotional communications from us by using the unsubscribe link within each email, updating your email preferences within your HighlightsFootball account settings menu, or by contacting us as provided below to have your contact information removed from our promotional email list or registration database. Even after you opt out from receiving promotional messages from us, you will continue to receive transactional messages from us regarding our Services. You can opt out of some notification messages in your account settings.

**Send “Do Not Track” Signals.**  Some browsers have incorporated “Do Not Track” (DNT) features that can send a signal to the websites you visit indicating you do not wish to be tracked. Because there is not yet a common understanding of how to interpret the DNT signal, our Services do not currently respond to browser DNT signals. You can use the range of other tools we provide to control data collection and use, including the ability to opt out of receiving marketing from us as described above.

Please see Cookies Policy above to understand how you can opt-out from certain cookies used though-out HighlightsFootball.

## What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

## Your Consent

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and our [Terms of Use](https://highlightsfootball.com/terms-of-use/). If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

## Our policy towards children

Our services are not directed to individuals under 16. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 16. If we become aware that a child under 16 has provided us with personal information, we will take steps to delete such information. If you become aware that a child has provided us with personal information, please contact us.

## Changes to this policy

We will notify you by email should there be any significant changes to this policy. We encourage you to review our privacy policy whenever you use our services to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy.

## Who can I ask if I have any additional questions?

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy and our practices, or you have reason to believe Highlightsfootball.com may have failed to adhere to this Privacy Policy, you can contact us using the [Contact page](https://highlightsfootball.com/contact-us/), email us on the given address.

**Email:** support@highlightsfootball.com

This document was last updated on  _May 20, 2018_
